[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：这就是这些东西的来源
&gt;&gt; Douglas: That's where the stuff came from and
因为初学者是用HyperCard编写的，我们知道它很容易
because the beginners were writing in HyperCard we know it's easy for
初学者使用基于事件的系统并进行异步编程。
beginners to use event based systems and to do asynchronous programming.
JavaScript在征服了浏览器之后，现在正在向服务器转移
JavaScript is now moving to the server after having conquered the browser it's
现在转移到服务器，它也在那里征服，
now moving to the server and it's conquering there too,
这很棒，因为它意味着我们开发的所有技能
which is great because it means all of the skill that we've developed and
在浏览器端做一些事情，我们现在可以将这些技能带回服务器端
doing stuff on the browser side we can now bring those skills back to the server side
这意味着你只需要真正掌握一种语言和
it means you only need to be really competent in one language and
这可以帮助节省一些时间。
that can help save some time.
不幸的是，服务器所做的与浏览器所做的有很大的不同。
Unfortunately what servers do is quite different than what browsers do.
事实上，它是如此的不同，以至于您需要一个相当不同的编程模型。
In fact it's so different that you need a fairly different programming model.
我们现在NODE中做服务器的事情。
We're doing server stuff now in node.
节点在JavaScript事件循环中实现Web服务器。
Node implements a web server in a JavaScript event loop.
这只是一个高性能的事件泵。
It's just a high performance event pump.
它非常高效，非常快，可以做大量的工作。
It's very efficient, very fast, can do a tremendous amount of work.
它第一次正确地执行文件I/O。
It does File I/O correctly for the first time.
回到Fortran和COBOL，文件I/O一直是阻塞的，
Going all the way back to Fortran and COBOL, File I/O has always been blocking,
在节点中，我们最终获得了非阻塞文件I/O。
and in node we finally get non blocking File I/O.
我们异步这样做，所以当你想读一个文件时，
We do it asynchronously so when you wanna read a file,
您传入一个文件名和一个回调函数，当读取文件时，
you pass in a filename and a callback function, and when the file is read,
它会调用你的回调函数，你会得到数据，这很棒。
it'll call your callback function and you get the data, and it's great.
因此程序不会阻止执行文件I/O，因为阻止会
And so the programs don't block on doing File I/O because blocking would
违反转弯定律，我们就永远不会违反转弯定律。
violate the law of turns and we'd never violate the law of turns.
我们注意到一切都是或可以是非阻塞的。
We note everything is or can be should be non blocking.
不幸的是，就像所有与JavaScript有关的事情一样，
Unfortunately, like everything that has anything to do with JavaScript,
节点并不是每件事都是正确的。
node doesn't get everything right.
对于Node，有几件事我真的很不满意，
A couple of things that I'm really unhappy about with node,
该节点具有许多烘焙到API中的同步函数。
is that node has a number of synchronous functions baked into the API.
而这些同步功能会阻塞一切。
And these synchronous functions block everything.
所以你从拥有一个非常快的高性能系统
And so you go from having a very fast high performance system
到一个非常慢的低性能系统，因为你阻塞了。
to a very slow low performance system instantly because you're blocking.
在完成同步调用之前，不会发生其他任何事情。
Nothing else gets to happen until the synchronous calls are done.
我想宣布那些同步功能为非法。
I would like to outlaw those synchronous functions.
不幸的是，我们在JavaScript社区中看到的
Unfortunately, what we've seen in the JavaScript community
如果你把一些非常愚蠢的东西放到API中，有网络开发人员会说，
is if you put something really stupid into an API, there are web developers that say,
我有权在那里使用它
I have a right to use it and there
节点中的这些同步功能是永远不应该使用的，但因为
are these synchronous functions in node which should never be used but because
他们在节点上，有人在使用他们，他们违反了转弯定律。
they're in node there are people using them and they violate the law of turns.
然后我不喜欢Required的东西，因为它也是阻塞的。
Then I don't like the requires thing because it is also blocking.
它在节点上第一个版本是异步的，
The very first version of it on node was asynchronous,
这是正确的做法，有人抱怨这太难了，
which is the correct way to do it and there were complaints that it's too hard,
它是由内到外的，我们只在早上开始工作
it's inside out and we only start things up in the morning
当我们打开服务器，所以一旦他们热身了，那就无关紧要了。
when we turn the servers on and so once they get warmed up then it doesn't matter.
这不是真的，然后我们总是让服务器启动和关闭。
That's not true and then we're bringing servers up and down all the time.
任何阻挡的东西都是坏事。
Anything which blocks is a bad thing.
幸运的是，在ES 6中，我们得到了一个新的模块系统，它取代了这一点，所以
Fortunately in ES 6 we're getting a new module system which obsoletes that, so
那样会更好。
that will be better.
但我们正在做的是，服务器与浏览器有很大的不同。
But what we're doing, servers are significantly different than browsers.
在服务器中，我们处理的不是事件，而是消息。
In a server we're not dealing with events we're dealing with messages.
现在消息来自网络。
Now message comes in from the network.
我们会做些什么，我们会发出另一条信息。
We'll do something, we'll send another message out.
都是关于信息的。
It's all about messaging.
节点服务器类似于参与者，它是一种接收消息和
A node server is actor like and that it's a thing which receives messages and
发送消息但我们的简单事件模型
sends messages but the simple events model that we
在浏览器上使用并不真正适合我们在服务器上所做的工作流。
use on the browser doesn't really fit the workflows that we do on a server.
例如，我们可能有一些东西需要几个连续的步骤，例如
For example, we may have things which take several sequential steps like
一个请求进来，我们接受这个请求，我们必须发送一些东西到数据库，
a request comes in, we take that request, we have to send something to a database,
找点东西回来，我们可以拿到这些信息，
get something back, we can take that information,
我们用它去另一个数据库取回东西。
we use that to go to another database and get stuff back.
这些事情中的每一件事都取决于前一件事。
Each of these things depends on the previous thing.
你怎么做到的？
How do you do that?
如果你不知道怎么做
If you don't know how to do it,
天真的方法是编写深度嵌套的事件处理程序。
the naive approach is to write deeply nested event handlers.
在一件事情的事件处理程序中，您发出下一个服务的请求，然后
In the event handler of one thing, you make a request of the next service and
在它的事件处理程序中，您发出下一个请求，该请求导致代码
in it's event handler you make the request of the next one that leads to code which
非常易碎，极难维护，性能低，
is extremely brittle, extremely hard to maintain, low performance,
都是坏事。
it's all bad stuff.
然后我们就有机会并行地做事情了。
Then we have the opportunity to do things in parallel.
可能是一个请求传入，我们可以同时访问几个系统
It might be a request comes in and we can go to several systems at the same time
因为请求不相互依赖，所以它们是独立的请求
because the requests are not dependent on each other so they're independent requests
通过并行，我们可以改变
and by going in parallel, we get to change the performance of
这件事很重要，因为不是等待每个人按顺序完成，
the thing significantly because instead of waiting for each to finish sequentially,
我们不需要花那么多时间，我们只需要等待
instead of taking that much time, we only have to wait for
这些东西中最慢的，通常时间要短得多。
the slowest of those things, which is usually a much shorter time.
我们可以显着改进我们的响应处理。
We can significantly improve our response processing.
不幸的是，这些请求中的每一个都可能到来
Unfortunately, each of these requests maybe coming
在意想不到的时间和意想不到的订单回来，你是如何处理的？
back at unexpected times and an unexpected orders and how do you deal with that?
你和一些人可能根本不会回来，你怎么处理这件事？
How do you and some might not come back at all and how do you deal with that?
所以这很难。
And so that's hard.
如果你不知道如何管理，那么天真的事情就是不要同时做。
If you don't know how to manage that naive thing is to not do it in parallel.
相反，使用深度嵌套的事件处理程序按顺序执行，这同样是，
Instead, do it sequentially with deeply nested event handlers, which is, again,
非常可怕。
quite awful.
然后，除此之外，你可能不得不处理有限的时间。
Then in addition to that, you may have to deal with limited time.
您可能有SLA或其他政策，要求我们必须在SO内得到响应
You may have SLAs or other policies which say we have to get a response within so
很多毫秒，如果我们不这样做，我们就得去B计划。
many milliseconds and if we don't, we have to go to plan B.
我们不能只是将请求挂起一段时间。
We can't just keep the request hanging for some amount of time.
然后我们必须处理取消。
And then we have to deal with cancellation.
如果我们去B计划，我们想停止所有不再必要的工作。
If we go to plan B, we want to stop all of the work which is no longer necessary.
如何在深度嵌套的事件处理程序中完成所有这些事情？
How do you do all of those things in deeply nested event handlers?